Mss.B.R124
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to J[ohn] Q[uincy] Adams, 1824 July 8 (Box 1)
    Original document located in the National Archives; Presented by Dr Julian P Boyd, June 1975.
  - Lines to her - J, December, 1824; 8" x 7 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    [also] Near the bank of a stream, melody. A.D. 2p. Poetry.
  - Review [of] Flora of North-America, January, 1824; 8" x 13 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    by Dr. W.P.C. Barton...1st & 2d volumes... Philadelphia, Nashville, Dr. of A.D.S: C.S. Rafinesque & Co. 6p.
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, April 10, 1824; 7 1/2" x 12 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
  - [Resolution to recommend the appointment of George Thomas Chapman to the professorship of history, geography and chronology], December 4, 1824; 8 1/2" x 11"; Transylvania University. Faculty
    signed C.S. Rafinesque, secy of faculty. Typed c. of D. 1p. (Original at Transylvania college)
  - A view of the contrast between the 3 systems or modes of social life & dealings., 1825; 7 1/2" x 12 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D.S. 4p.
  - Book 2d- Neobotan-or new plants of North America from Hooker, Sims, Lindley &c with some exotic new genera, (circa 1825); Rafinesque, C. S., (Constantine Samuel ), 1783-1840
  - Letter to the Board of trustees of Transylvania university, May 30, 1825; 8 1/2" x 11"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Transylvania university, Typed c. of L. 1p. (Original at Transylvania College)
  - [Resolution regarding the leave of absence requested by C.S. Rafinesque], June 7, 1825; 8 1/2" x 11"; Transylvania University. Faculty
    signed C.S. Rafinesque, secretary of the faculty. Typed c. of D. 1p. (Original at Transylvania college)
  - Letter to the Board of trustees of Transylvania university, June 14, 1825; 8 1/2" x 11"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Transylvania university, Typed c. of L. 1p. (Original at Transylvania college)
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, June 16, 1825; 7 3/4" x 12 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Lexington, A.L.S. 2p. and add.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, June 28, 1825; 7 3/4" x 12 1/4"; Tarascon, Louis Anastasius, b. 1759
    Shippingport, Ky., A.L.S. 1p. and add. In French.
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, August 1, 1825; 8 1/4" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Washington city, A.L.S. 3p. and add.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, August 16, 1825; 8" x 10"; Tarascon, Louis Anastasius, b. 1759
    Shippingport, Ky., A.L.S. 1p. and add. In French
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, August 20, 1825; 7 3/4" x 12 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
  - Letter to [C.S. Rafinesque], August 24, 1825; 8" x 9 1/2"; Collins, Zaccheus, 1764-1831
    Philadelphia, A.L. 2p.
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, September 12, 1825; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 3p. and add.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, September 29, 1825; 7 1/2" x 9 1/2"; Tarascon, Louis Anastasius, b. 1759
    Shippingport, Ky., A.L.S. 2p. In French.
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, October 10, 1825; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. and add.
  - Receipt for $35 borrowed from Zaccheus Collins, October 11, 1825; 7 3/4" x 5 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Philadelphia, A.D.S. 1p. and end.
  - Letter to D. Raymond, November 10, 1825; 8 1/2" x 11"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Cincinnati, Typed c. of L. 2 leaves. (Original at Transylvania College)
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, November 22, 1825; 7 3/4" x 12 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Frankfort, Ky., A.L.S. 3p. and add.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, December 26, 1825; 8 1/2" x 11"; Raymond, D.
    Lexington, Ky., Typed c. of L. 1p. (Original at Transylvania College)
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, January 12, 1826; 7 1/2" x 12 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Lexington, Ky., A.L.S. 3p. and add. (P.1 contains a printed circular about his patent, divitial invention)
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, March 1, 1826; 7 1/2" x 12 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Lexington, Ky., A.L.S. 2p. and add. (P. 3 contains a printed circular about his patent, divitial invention)
  - Letter to Zaccheus Collins, August 14, 1826; 8" x 9 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Germantown, A.L.S. 3p. and add.
  - Letter to [C.S. Rafinesque], August 16, 1826; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Collins, Zaccheus, 1764-1831
    Philadelphia A.L.S. 1p. and end.
  - Receipt for $2.10 issued to Z[accheus] Collins for freight on boxes for C.S. Rafinesque, August 29, 1826; 8" x 4"; C. Price & Morgan
    Philadelphia, D. 1p. and end.
  - Receipt for $15 borrowed from Zaccheus Collins, August 30, 1826; 7 1/4" x 3 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
  - [Constitution], 1826?; 8" x 12 3/4"; Benevolent Mutual Institution of Philadelphia
    D. 4p. (In C.S. Rafinesque's hand) Also: list of members, 2p., and occupations of members, 2p.
  - Indication of medical plants from North America., 1828; 8" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Philadelphia, A.D.S. 28p.
  - Account of 32 N. sp. of plants from Florida, [Circa 1828-183-]; Rafinesque, C. S., (Constantine Samuel ), 1783-1840
  - [Descriptions of 75 n.sp., followed by abstracts of Kunth's works], [Circa 1828-1830]
  - Letter to C.S. Rafinesque, January 22, 1828; 8" x 9 1/2"; Clinton, George W. (George William), 1807-1885
    Albany, A.L.S. 1p. and add.
  - Letter to [C.S.] Rafinesque, April 17, 1828; 8" x 10"; Société royale d'horticulture des Pays-Bas
    Bruxelles, L.S.: Drassier (?). 2p. In French.
  - Letter to [C.S. Rafinesque], October 8, 1828; 7 1/2" x 12 3/4"; Lawrence, G. K.
    New Lebanon, A.L.S. 4p.
  - Prunus (cerasus) rotundifolia, Raf. 1829 or Pr. Cladopus, Raf. 1832 (drawing)., 1829-1832
  - Neophyton, or new plants, genera & species from North America. Books 1,2,3, 1830; Rafinesque, C. S., (Constantine Samuel ), 1783-1840
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, September 28, 1830; 8" x 9 3/4"; Lanthois, Georgette Louisa, d. c. 1834
    Bordeaux, A.L.S. 3p. and add. In French.
  - Memoires sur l'origine des nations negres, ou introduction a l'histoire negres indigenes d'Asie, d'Afrique, polynesie, Amerique et Europe., 1831; Rafinesque, C. S., (Constantine Samuel ), 1783-1840
  - Account of the largest tree near Philadelphia (for the Saturday Evening Post), 1831 May; Rafinesque, C. S., (Constantine Samuel ), 1783-1840
  - Summons for Daniel Parker, Septmeber 10, 1831; 13 1/4" x 5"; Philadelphia. District Court
    administrator of Zaccheus Collins, to appear on the first Monday of December to answer Constantine Samuel Rafinesque. Philadelphia, Printed D. filled in in ms. S: John Lisle, prothonotary of the District court. 1p. and end.
  - Mémoires sur l'origine des nations nègres, 1831; 8 1/4" x 13 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    ou introduction à l'histoire des nègres indigènes d'Asie, d'Afrique, Polynèsie, Amérique & Europe...Philadelphia, A.D.S. 24p. In French. ---- Seconde partie...1831. A.D.S. 48p. In French. ---- Additions aux Mémoires sur les races negres Asiatiques. A.D.S. 32p. 8 1/4" x 13 1/2" In French
  - Bill against the estate of Zacheus Collins., October 19, 1831; 8" x 13"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D.S. 1p. and end.
  - Letter to [C.S. Rafinesque], December 11, 1831; 8" x 10 1/4"; Rafinesque, Emilia
    A.L.S. 5p. In Italian.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, December 14, 1831; 8" x 10 1/4"; Lanthois, Georgette Louisa, d. c. 1834
    Bordeaux, A.L.S. 6p. add. In French.
  - Mantissa ad flora Floridana S America Sept supplementum & appendix Books 1,2,3, 1832; Rafinesque, C. S., (Constantine Samuel ), 1783-1840
  - Description of the Streblanthus, a new American genus of plants and enquiries on its natural affinities., [Circa 1832]; Rafinesque, C. S., (Constantine Samuel ), 1783-1840
  - Florula apalachensis, [Circa 1832]
  - Rafinesque vs Parker. Notes of the arbitration., 1832 March 29
  - Rafinesque vs Parker Abstract of letters from C.S. Rafinesque., 1832 March 29
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, April 18, April 24, 1832; 8" x 10 1/4"; Lanthois, Georgette Louisa, d. c. 1834
    Bordeaux, A.L.S. 4p. add. In French.
  - Notice relative to the choosing of arbitrators for the case of C.S. Rafinesque vs. Daniel Parker, January 10, 1832; 8" x 7"; Philadelphia. District Court
    administrator of Zacheus Collins; Philadelphia, Printed D. filled in in ms. 1p. and end.
  - Letter to William Rawle, February 2, 1832; 5" x 7 3/4"; Pickering, Charles, 1805-1878
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. and add.
  - Letter to Wm. Rawle, February 3, 1832; 3 3/4" x 5 3/4"; Brown, P. A.
    Printed form filled in in ms. 1p., add. and end. Notice of meeting or arbitrators in case of Rafinesque vs. Parker.
  - Letter to Wm. Rawle, May 16, 1832; 5" x 8"; Brown, P. A.
    [ca.?] A.L.S. 1p. and add. Re case of Rafinesque vs. Parker.
  - Letter to Constantine Rafinesque, June 5, 1832; 8" x 10 3/4"; Rafinesque, Emilia
    A.L.S. 4p. add. In Italian. (Mutilated)
  - Letter to [C.S.] Rafinesque, October 16, 1832; 8" x 10 1/4"; Société de géographie (France)
    Paris, L.S: Jomard. 1p. In French.
  - Letter to C.S. Rafinesque, December 4, 1832; 8 1/2" x 12 1/2"; Rafinesque, Emilia
    A.L.S. 3p. and add. In Italian.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, December 6, 1832; 8" x 10 1/4"; Lanthois, Georgette Louisa, d. c. 1834
  - Graphic Systems of North America, 1833; Rafinesque, C. S., (Constantine Samuel ), 1783-1840
  - Letter to Constantine Rafinesque, May 22, 1833; 8 1/4" x 12"; Rafinesque, Emilia
    A.L.S. 2p. and add. In Italian.
  - Letter to [C. S.] Rafinesque, June 9, 1833; 8" x 10 1/4"; Société de géographie (France)
    Paris, L.S: Roux de Rochelle. 1p. and add. In French.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, July 28, 1833; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Beck, Lewis C. (Lewis Caleb), 1798-1853
    Albany, A.L.S. 3p. and add.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, September 12, 1833; 7 3/4" x 10"; Van Heuvel, J. A. (Jacob Adrien), 1787-1874
    Heuvelton, St. Lawrence co., N.Y., A.L.S. 3p. and add.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, October 23, 1833; 7 3/4" x 13"; Van Heuvel, J. A. (Jacob Adrien), 1787-1874
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, November 9, 1833; 7 1/2" x 9 1/4"; Swainson, William, 1789-1855
    A.L.S. 1p. and add.
  - Letter to [C. S. Rafinesque], December 9, 1833; 7 3/4" x 10"; Torrey, John, 1796-1873
    New York, A.L.S. 2p.
  - [Contract with the impresario of the Italian opera in the U.S. by which Emilia [Rafinesque] Winston is engaged for 10 months, 1834-1835, to "sing, gesticulate and recite"], April, 1834; 8" x 9 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Philadelphia, D. 4p.
  - Letter to Constantine Rafinesque, January 28, 1834; 8 1/4" x 10 3/4"; Rafinesque, Emilia
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, February 5, 1834; 8" x 10"; Torrey, John, 1796-1873
  - Letter to [C.S.] Rafinesque, April 1, 1834; 8" x 10"; Torrey, John, 1796-1873
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, August 20, 1834; 8" x 10"; Corroy, François
    Tabasco, A.L.S. 12p. In French.
  - Letter to C.S. Rafinesque, September 7, 1834; 8 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Short, Charles Wilkins, 1794-1863
    Lexington, Ky., A.L.S. 4p.add.
  - Letter to C.S. Rafinesque, September 30, 1834; 8" x 9 1/2"; Torrey, John, 1796-1873
    New York, A.L.S. 3p.add. (P.1 is a printed circular pertaining to the College of physicians and surgeons of the University of the state of New-York)
  - Letter to [C.S.] Rafinesque, December 24, 1834; 8" x 10"; Société de géographie (France)
    Paris, L.S.: Jomard. 2p. and add. In French.
  - [Pages from a letter book(?)], June-February, 1834-1835; 7 1/2" x 11 1/2"; Allen, Rhodes & Co.
    D. 4p.
  - Letter to C. S. Rafinesque, February 24, 1835; 8" x 10 1/2"; Eyriès, Alex
    Le Havre, A.L.S. 1p. and add. In French. Rafinesque Papers - H
  - Letter to [Daniel] Parker, April 28, 1835; 8" x 9 3/4"; Rawle, William, 1759-1836
  - [Rafinesque vs Parker] Notice of referees in the case of Rafinesque [vs Parker], 1835 May 30
  - New orrare - plants of North America chiefly, collected from various late authors..., 1836; 8 1/4" x 13"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D.S. 44p.
  - Florula Alabamensis & Floridana, 1836
  - Letter to John W. Ashmead, December 23, 1836; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Parker, Daniel, 1782-1846
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. and add.
  - Letter to S. S. Haldeman, Marietta,Pa., Oct. 15, 1838; 13" x 8 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. and add. Sale of Shells. Deposited by the Academy of natural sciences of Philadelphia, May 1854.
  - [Autikon botanikon. Nos. 1160-1400], [Circa 1840]
  - Letter to [John] Lindley, May, 1840; 8" x 12 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    Philadelphia, A. copy of L.S. 4p. (Note: Copy of the botanical letter to Dr. Lindley printed in the Amenities of nature, n.2)
  - 109 On 3 sp. of Typha, 110 Two new genera of Umbelliferous plants from Kentucky, 111 On 12 N. sp of plants from Illionois, 112 On 17 n. sp. of plants from..., Undated
  - Monography of vitis, Undated
  - Notes, Undated
  - [Miscellaneous notes], Undated
  - The Graphic Systems of the Ancient american and chinese Nations., Undated
  - Ecpexis n.g., Undated
  - Description of a new genus of fossil bivalve-shell, Undated
  - Letter to [C.S. Rafinesque] n.d., undated; Collins, Zaccheus, 1764-1831
    A.L.S. with initials. 2p.
  - Miscellaneous notes relative to the case of C.S. Rafinesque vs. Daniel Parker, undated; 6 1/2" x 8", 8" x 13 1/2"; Parker, Daniel, 1782-1846
    [administrator for Zaccheus Collins, deceased.] A.D. 12p.
  - Analytical notice of the Medical flora of the United States of Prof. Rafinesque, undated; 8 1/4" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    2 vol...Philadelphia, 1828 and 1830. A.D. 2p.
  - Bibliotheca Americana, undated; 7 3/4" x 12 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    or books on America and the Americans...N.1. A.D.S. 32p.(and 3 loose leaves).
  - Book 43d or Z. Y. Materials for the history of the American nations, undated; 8 1/2" x 13"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    their annals, traditions, chronology,ethnography, languages, monuments &c., in North and South America, the Antilles &c...1839. A.D.S. 40p.
  - Botanical miscellany & extracts chiefly on new families, undated; 8" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    genera & species...1830 to 1834. A.D.S. 44p.
  - Catalogue of the seeds of Mr. Rafinesque., undated; 7 3/4" x 12 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 3p.
  - The cause of the Indians, signed Veritas., undated; 8" x 13"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 1p.
  - Désignation de la durée des plantes &c., undated; 7 3/4" x 12 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D.S. 2p.
  - Enumeration historique et biographique depuis Linneus., undated; 8" x 12 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 12p. (8 blank)
  - Florula economica Sicula, or an account of the properties of some Sicilian plants., undated; 8 1/2" x 12 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 2p.
  - Florula Lyncemontana, or the vernal flora of the Catskill mountains containing the catalogue of the plants found on the north-east side of the catskill mountains and in the surrounding country, undated; 7 3/4" x12 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    in June 1817, by Messrs. Rafinesque & Knevels. A.D. 1p.
  - Ideas on harmonies of nature., undated; 8 1/4" x 12 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
  - Index - Flora of North America, undated; 8 1/4" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    plants, trees &c. seen, described, collected, &c. chiefly new, by C.S. Rafinesque, between 1802 to 1804 & 1815 to 1835 &c... A.D.S. 42p.
  - Lectures on various subjects [delivered at Transylvania university]., undated; 8" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    1820-1824. A.D.S. 72p.(23 blank) and 32 loose p.
  - Materials for the Annals of nature., undated; 8 1/2" x 12"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 4p.
  - [Miscellaneous botanical notes, being chiefly lists of new genera and species found in works of different authors], undated; 7 1/2" x 12 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 51 items in 151 p. ca.
  - [Miscellaneous notes on medical botany.], undated; 8 1/4" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 19 items in 77 pages. ca.
  - [Miscellaneous notes pertaining to grapes and wine making], undated; 8 1/4" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 14p.
  - [Notes relative to] herbarium Rafinesquianum., undated; 8" x 12 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 16p.
  - [Outline for a] lecture on American history., undated; 7 3/4" x 12 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
  - Outlines of American ethnology, undated; 8 1/4" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    or enumeration and account of the materials which exist for the history of the native tribes of America before the discovery of the continent by Columbus. A.D. 60p.
  - Plan of the American botany & zoology., undated; 7 1/2" x 12 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A(?) D. 4p.
  - Plants of Kentucky, &c., undated; 8 1/2" x 9 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    sent to Europe in 1822 to several botanists. A.D. 8p.(3 blank)
  - Principes fondamentaux de la sométrie, ou rudimens de la géometrie des corps., undated; 8" x 12 3/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D.S. 3p. and 3 slips laid in.
  - Propriétés et usages des plantes., undated; 7" x 9 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
  - Scientific exploration of North America and the south of Europe,during 32 years from 1800 to 1832., undated; 8 1/4" x 13 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
  - Série de letters & observations botaniques addressées à M. De Candolle... 1830-1832., undated; 8" x 13 1/4"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D.S. 32p. In French. Contains also copies of a few letters to other persons, 1831-1839.
  - To the public., undated; 8" x 13"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 4p. (and small enc.)
  - Utility of some European plants., undated; 8 1/4" x 13 1/2", 8 1/4" x 13 1/2"; Rafinesque, C. S. (Constantine Samuel), 1783-1840
    A.D. 5p. Contains also: Notes on the cyclopedia of plants of Loudon, Lindley & Sowerby...London,1829...1830. A.D.S. 17p.
  - Letter to [C.S.] Rafinesque, March 28, undated; 8" x 10"; Morelli
    A.L.S. 1p. and add. In Italian.
  - (Misc. notes on medical botany), undated; Rafinesque, C. S., (Constantine Samuel ), 1783-1840
  - Images
    - Ojibwa pictographs, 1833; 1.0 Item(s)
    - Osage pictographs, 1804-1818; 1.0 Item(s)
    - Walam Olum, 1833; 1.0 Item(s)
    - Walam Olum, 1833; 1.0 Item(s)
    - Ojibwa pictographs, 1833; 1.0 Item(s)
    - Osage pictographs, 1804-1818; 1.0 Item(s)
    - Walam Olum, 1833; 1.0 Item(s)
    - Walam Olum, 1833; 1.0 Item(s)
- Letters to de Candolle, 1817-1839 (Box 4)
  Letters to Augustin Pyramus de Candolle 1778-1841
  Photostats of 19 A.L.S (negative and positive)
  From originals in the possesion of the Arhives du Conservatoire botanique de Geneve. Presented by Dr. William J. Robbins March 1957.
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1817 Dec 15 (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1818 Dec 30 (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1819 May 4 (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1819 June 5 (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1820 April 10 (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1821 Feb 15 (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1830 March (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1830, May (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1830, June (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1830, July (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1830, Oct (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1830, Nov (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1830, Dec (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1831, May (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1831, June (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1831 August (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1832 Oct 25 (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1839 May 5 (Box 4)
  - Letter to de Candolle, 1839 Dec 10 (Box 4)